# Bernard Yang

604-616-8765 • linkedin.com/in/bernard-yang • bernardyang@outlook.com • LIC-2023-0043591-R01

# PROFILE

A Level 2 General Insurance Salesperson with 3 years experience in the insurance industry. A team player who is also capable of finding solutions independently. Currently working in a position assisting producers with a book of business primarily in personal lines. Seeking a challenging position with an opportunity to learn the more complex side of commercial lines.

# EXPERIENCE

# **Customer Service Representative**

Insureline Brokers

May 2023 - Present

Vancouver, BC

- Utilize computer programming knowledge to prefill 100's of questionnaires, disclosures, LOBs saving time for team members and producers
- Process PolicyCentre renewals, out-of-province transfers, and all other incidental ICBC transactions including Family Private Auto
- Help producers get quotes via Applied Rating System, get binding through underwriters, get quotes for hard to place policies through special market
- Use Applied Epic to enter activities, endorsements, cancellations, invoice payments, create policy shells, create CSIO applications

**Real Estate Agent** 

July 2018 - July 2020

Macdonald Realty

Vancouver, BC

- · Attended agents' open house and analyzed sales data on MLS to accurately perform comparative market analysis
- Prepared all documents pertaining to contract of purchase and sale, and listing agreements

#### **Customer Service Representative**

June 2015 - Jan 2018

Tony Lau Insurance

Vancouver, BC

- · Helped in-house, walk-in clients, producers with home, travel, and ICBC insurance
- Experience working with Applied TAM and PowerQuote

#### EDUCATION

Diploma in Web Development

Lighthouse Labs

May 2021 - Aug 2021

Remote, BC

2009 - 2011

Kwantlen Polytechnic University

Richmond, BC

#### INSURANCE TOOLKIT

**Diploma in Business Administration** 

- Applied Epic, Applied Rating System, Applied TAM, PowerQuote
- Family Portal, Gore Mutual Portal (Guidewire), Intact Portal, Wawanesa Portal

### SKILLS

- Intermediate knowledge of Microsoft Excel, and Outlook
- Working knowledge of computer programming languages including Python, JavaScript, SQL
- · Cantonese conversant